# Dayamani Orsu

Phone: +91-7674955435

Mail to: <u>dayamani.orsu23@gmail.com</u>

Current Location: Hyderabad

\_\_\_\_\_

# **Objective**

Has 5 years of experience in Talent Acquisition Management, Operations, Administration and compliance and Benefits. I aspire to enhance my professional skills in a stable and dynamic workplace to succeed in an environment of growth and excellence which provide me self-development and help me achieve personal as well as organizational goal.

#### Skills

- Employee Onboarding
- New Employee Orientation
- Compensation Structuring
- Staff Management
- Recruitment and Hiring
- Records Management
- Payroll Coordination
- Payroll Administration
- Employee Relations
- Compliance
- Compensation and Benefits
- Offboarding
- Background Check
- Employee Engagement

#### **EXPERIENCE:**

04/2022- Current

# **People Operations Specialist**

Procensol (Roboyo Hyperautomation India Pvt Ltd)- Hyderabad, India

- Organized recruitment activities including job postings, candidate sourcing, interviewing, selection and background checks.
- Conducted onboarding and offboarding process for new and departing employees.
- Drafted offer letters for new hires in line with company policy and procedures.
- Coordinated with the IT team for login credentials.
- Handled Assets allocation for all the regions.
- Assisted with payroll processing of benefits programs.
- Handled Group Health Insurance for new and existing employees.
- Maintained accurate records in personnel files and database.
- Responded promptly to inquiries from employees about benefits or other HR

topics.

- Developed and implemented policies and procedures related to HR operations.
- Analyzed data to identify trends in employee performance, engagement, attrition and compensation.
- Worked with management to create performance management, employee development, and employee compensation strategies.
- Managed payroll processing activities including time tracking, benefits, administration, compliance and compensation calculations.

## 05/2018-06/2020

#### **Human Resources Executive**

Valmiki Group- Hyderabad, India

- Reviewed job descriptions for accuracy and relevance to current needs of the organization.
- Organized recruitment activities including job postings, candidate sourcing, interviewing and selection.
- Drafted offer letters for new hires in line with company policy and procedures.
- Created and maintained personnel records in accordance with legal requirements.
- Managed payroll processing activities including time tracking, benefits administration and compensation calculations.
- Coordinated with the management for Offboarding activities.
- Conducted employee engagement activities.

### 06/2016- 02/2017

#### Sales executive

Tradebull Securities- Hyderabad, India

- Reviewed job descriptions for accuracy and relevance to current needs of the organization.
- Organized recruitment activities including cold calling, candidate sourcing.
- Coordinated with the sales for the interviewing and selection.
- Maintained accurate records in personnel files and database.

### 05/2015-01/2016

#### **HR Recruiter**

Xlent Recruitment Solutions- Hyderabad, India

- Reviewed job descriptions for accuracy and relevance to current needs of the organization.
- Organized recruitment activities including cold calling, candidate sourcing and interviewing.
- Maintained accurate records in personnel files and database.

## **Certifications**

| Туре          | Awarded On     |  |
|---------------|----------------|--|
| HR Generalist | September 2023 |  |

# **Educational Details**

| Institution              | Qualification | Percentage | Passed Out Year |
|--------------------------|---------------|------------|-----------------|
| ASIST                    | B.Tech        | 71.2%      | 04-2013         |
| Sri Chaitanya Jr College | Intermediate  | 85.1%      | 04-2009         |
| R.C.M High School        | SSC           | 85%        | 04-2007         |